Guide to the R. G. Davis Papers Relating to Dario Fo
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Cowan, Suzanne / Kidron, Michael - translation, publication, 1979 (Box 7)
  Contains material regarding the English-language translation of "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!," specifically handwritten and typescript notes, and clippings.
- Additional correspondence - Fo, 1979-1983 (Box 7)
  Contains material regarding "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!"
- Dario Fo - Nobel Prize, 1970-1997 (Box 7)
  Contains corrected writings, correspondence, newspaper clippings, flyers and photocopies.
- Paul Leavin, 1980 (Box 7)
  Contains correspondence, handwritten notes, "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!" showbill, contracts, newspaper clippings, financial material, and photocopies.
- Tapes of all shows, 1981-05-27-1983; 1 (Box 7)
  Contains material regarding Ann Arbor, Michigan, and San Francisco, California performances of "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!," and material regarding Jane Dornacker and Female Parts.
  Separated Materials
  Audiocassettes housed separately.
  - Empty Space - Seattle, WWP., 1981-05-27; 1 (Box 8)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of audiovisual materials may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - WWP / S.F., 1983-04-23; 1 (Box 8)
  - WWP! / S.F., 1983-04; 1 (Box 8)
  - Female Parts - Awaken / Punk Mama, 1983-01-19; 1 (Box 8)
  - [Rehearsal] / Jane - Female Parts, 1982-12-07; 1 (Box 8)
  - Female Parts, 1983; 1 (Box 8)
  - Jane / Female Parts / [Rehearsal], 1982-12-17; 1 (Box 8)
  - Female Parts - Same Old Story, 1983-01-19; 1 (Box 8)
  - We Won't Pay - Ann Arbor, 1982-02; 1 (Box 8)
  - WWP - Ann Arbor, 1982; 1 (Box 8)
  - Ann Arbor - WWP. (1-2), 1982-06-29; 1 (Box 8)
- Dario Fo tapes - of all shows, 1979-06-05-1981-02-17; 1 (Box 7)
  Contains material regarding Jane Dornacker, "Female Parts," and "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!"
  Audiocassettes housed seperately.
  - Piero Sciotto discussing Non Si Paga, 1979-08-13; 1 (Box 8)
  - Non Si Paga - Sciotto - V - VI, 1979-08-13; 1 (Box 8)
  - Piero Sciotto - Hastings on the Hudson, NY - Songs, 1979-06-14; 1 (Box 8)
  - Non si paga Act II, 1979-06-05; 1 (Box 8)
  - Reading, New Jersey - Non Si Paga Act I, 1979-06-05; 1 (Box 8)
  - WWP NYU - Act I, 1980-05; 1 (Box 8)
  - We Won't Pay - NY Chelsea Theatre, 1980-12-03; 1 (Box 8)
  - We Won't Pay, 1981-02-17; 1 (Box 8)
  - We Won't Pay - N..Y., 1981-02-17; 1 (Box 8)
  - NYC Chelsea Theatre - Act I. - We Won't Pay, 1980-12-05; 1 (Box 8)
  - Chelsea NYC - We Won't Pay - Act I. 1st part (Act II.), 1980-12-03; 1 (Box 8)
  - Sciotto - Non si paga - III - IV, 1979-08-13; 1 (Box 8)
- Other audiovisual material, 1950-1981
  - Accidental - Act II, 1980-03-08; 1 (Box 8)
  - "Richard Lichtman (3&4) #9" [struck through], 1980-03-29; 1 (Box 8)
    Contains material regarding Accidental Death of an Anarchist.
  - Non si paga - Act I. - Vancouver Tamahous, 1980-09-11; 1 (Box 8)
  - Accidental Death (3)(4), 1980-02-17; 1 (Box 8)
  - Accidental Death - 1 + 2, 1980-03-09; 1 (Box 8)
  - Act. III Vancouver, 1980-09-12; 1 (Box 8)
    Contains material regarding "Non si paga," performed in Vancouver, British Columbia.
  - WWP - LAAT - Act II., 1981-09-21; 1 (Box 8)
  - Act I., LAAT - W.W.P., 1981-09-10; 1 (Box 8)
    Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of audiovsiual materials may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Act II. 4th prev LAAT - matinee, LAAT - We Won't Pay, 1981-09-06; 1 (Box 8)
  - Act I., LAAT - We Won't Pay, 1981-09-06; 1 (Box 8)
  - Accidental Death - Canada, 1980-03-09; 1 (Box 8)
  - Vancouver Tamahous - Non si paga, 1980-09-12; 1 (Box 8)
  - "Aronowitz" [struck through], 1980-03-29; 1 (Box 8)
    Contains sound recordings from "Accidental Death of an Anarchist."
  - We Won't Pay - LAAT, 1981; 1 (Box 8)
  - We Won't Pay, undated; 1 (Box 8)
    Listed tracks include Sirens - Police; Ambulance Arrives; Sirens; Gunshots - Crowd.
  - 1 - Dario Fo / Music, 1980-03; 1 (Box 8)
    Contains music to "Accidental Death of an Anarchist," as well as "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!," performed in Toronto, Ontario.
  - 2 - Dario Fo / Music, 1980-03; 1 (Box 8)
    Contains music to "Accidental Death of an Anarchist," performed in Toronto, Ontario.
  - Female Parts - Tape "A" - pre-show music, undated; 1 (Box 8)
  - We Won't Pay, undated; 1 (Box 8)
    Listed tracks include Police sirens; Ambulance approach; Sirens; Screams and Gunshots (guns 15 sec. only).
  - We Won't Pay! master, undated; 1 (Box 8)
  - WWP - sound tapes, undated; 1 (Box 8)
  - Le Canzoni Di Dario Fo Vol. 2, 1977; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - Dario Fo ‎– Mistero Buffo Vol. 2 - Il Teatro Di Dario Fo, 1980; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - Various ‎– To Our Friends (Mario L. F. Russo), 1965; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - Rocco de Russo / Ria Sampieri - Italian Comic Dialogue, circa 1950s; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - Mia Martini ‎– Incontro Con Mia Martini, 1978; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - Various ‎– Celebri Marce Italiane, 1977; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - Ordine! Per Dio.ooo.ooo.ooo di Dario Fo, 1972; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - Dario Fo ‎– Canzoni Dallo Spettacolo Di Dario Fo, circa 1972; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - Collettivo Teatrale La Comune ‎– 1° Guerra Di Popolo In Cile, 1973; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - Dario Fo ‎– Mistero Buffo Vol. 3 - Il Teatro Di Dario Fo, 1980; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - Dario Fo ‎– Mistero Buffo Vol. 4 - Il Teatro Di Dario Fo, 1980; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - Dario Fo ‎– Mistero Buffo Vol. 5 - Il Teatro Di Dario Fo, 1980; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - Dario Fo ‎– Mistero Buffo Vol. 1 - Il Teatro Di Dario Fo, 1980; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - Collettivo Teatrale La Comune ‎– 2° Guerra Di Popolo In Cile, 1973; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - La Comune, Dario Fo, Franca Rame ‎– Basta Con I Fascisti!, undated; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - La Comune ‎– Pum Pum! Chi È? La Polizia!, 1972; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - Vorrei Morire Anche Stasera Se Dovessi Pensare Che Non E' Servito A Niente, circa 1970; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
  - Premiata Forneria Marconi ‎– Prime Impressioni, 1976; 1 (Box 9 (Record album storage))
- We Won't Pay! - Los Angeles Actors' Theatre (LAAT), contact prints, 1981-10 (Box 10 (Oversize))
  Contains contact prints of both Act I and Act II, as well as handwritten notes on the backs of the images.
- Posters from "Female Parts" and "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!", circa 1980s (Box 10 (Oversize))
  Includes material relating to Jane Dornacker performances.